var chapter2 = '{"quizName":"ERP Chapter 2","questions":[{"question":"Which term relates to the technical capabilities that allow systems to connect with one another through standardized interfaces called Web services?","options":["Enterprise Resource Planning","Supply Chain Management","Architecture","Service-Oriented Architecture","None of the above"],"answerIndex":3},{"question":"Which term refers to the technical structure of the software, how users interact with the software, and how the software is physically managed on computer hardware?","options":["Architecture","Supply Chain Management","Enterprise Resource Planning","Service Oriented Architecture","None of the above"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Which of the following is used to integrate several client-server applications and create enterprise mash-ups, or composite applications?","options":["Management System","Accounting System","Enterprise System","All of the above","Web Services"],"answerIndex":4},{"question":"Which system connects a company’s ERP system to those of its customers?","options":["Application Platform","Customer Relationship Management (CRM)","Enterprise Solution","Product Lifecycle Management (PLM)","None of the above"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Which of the following systems helps companies administer the processes of research, design, and product management?","options":["Application Platform","Customer Relationship Management (CRM)","Enterprise Solution","Product Lifecycle Management (PLM)","None of the above"],"answerIndex":3},{"question":"Which program is the “operating system” for an entire company’s business processes?","options":["Microsoft Vista","Linux","SAP NetWeaver","SAP Prolific","None of the above"],"answerIndex":2},{"question":"The highest organizational level in SAP ERP is the","options":["Vendor","Client","Material Master","Plant","None of the above"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Which of the following is(are) used to represent the structure of an enterprise?","options":["Organizational Data","Project Management","Client","Plant","Lifecycle Data Management"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Which of the following terms refers to an organizational element that performs multiple functions and is relevant to several processes? ","options":["Warehouse","Procurement ","Plant","Fulfillment ","Lifecycle Data Management"],"answerIndex":2},{"question":"How many company codes can a plant belong to?","options":["One","Two","Three","Any Number"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Which of the following master data is used in numerous processes?","options":["Material Master","Plant","Company Code","Customer Master","Vendor Master"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Materials that are created by the production process from other materials are referred to as _____________","options":["Finished Goods (FERT)","Semi-finished Goods (HALB)","Trading Goods (HAWA)","Raw Materials","None of the above"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"What type of materials is purchased from a vendor?","options":["Trading Goods","Finished Goods (FERT)","Semi-finished Goods (HALB)","Material Types","None of the above"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Materials that are purchased from an external source (a vendor) and used in the production process are known as  ______________","options":["Finished Goods (FERT)","Semi-finished Goods (HALB)","Trading Goods (HAWA)","Raw Materials","None of the above"],"answerIndex":3},{"question":"Which of the following terms refers to materials with similar characteristics?","options":["Material Master","Material Group","Transaction Data","Material number","None of the above"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"____________ reflect(s) the consequences of executing process steps.","options":["Material Groups","Organizational Data","Transaction Data","Project Management","None of the above"],"answerIndex":2},{"question":"Financial accounting (FI) documents, management accounting or controlling (CO) documents, and material documents are referred to as","options":["Transaction Documents","Transaction Data","Material Group","Virtual Documents","None of the above"],"answerIndex":3},{"question":"Which term is generally used to describe the ways that users can view and analyze data to help them make decisions and complete their tasks?","options":["Reporting","Evaluating","Characteristics","Period Definition","Online Analytic Processing (OLAP)"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Which of the following is(are) used to capture specified transaction data in an aggregated and summarized form that enables users to analyze the data as needed.","options":["Reporting","Evaluating","Information Structures","Period Definition","Online Analytic Processing (OLAP)"],"answerIndex":2},{"question":"Which of the following identify tasks that are scheduled to be completed in a process?","options":["Online Lists","Parameters","Information Structures","Work Lists","Period definitions"],"answerIndex":3},{"question":"The architecture of an enterprise system refers to the technical structure of the software, how users interact with the software, and how the software is physically managed on computer hardware.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"The three layers of the “three-tier client-server architecture” are the presentation layer, windows layer, and data layer.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"When you access the Internet, your browser is the presentation layer.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Scalability is the ability of the hardware and software to support a greater number of users easily over time.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Service-oriented architecture (SOA) is the fundamental concept behind systems connecting through standardized interfaces called Web services.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Enterprise resource planning (ERP) focuses on the internal operations of an organization.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Inter-company processes take place within a single company. ","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Customer relationship management (CRM) systems connect a company’s ERP system to its accounting software system.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Supply chain management (SCM) systems help companies execute the processes of research, design, and product management. ","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Application platforms serve as a type of \'enterprise operating system\' for a company’s ES landscape by allowing all of the various systems to communicate seamlessly with one another as well as with systems outside the company.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Current versions of the SAP business suite can’t run on SAP NetWeaver.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"SAP NetWeaver is the “operating system” for an entire company’s business processes.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Organizational data are used to represent the structure of an enterprise.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"A company code is the highest organizational level in SAP ERP.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"A client represents each company within an enterprise.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Material master are organizational elements that performs multiple functions and is relevant to several processes.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"A building can house only a single plant.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"A plant can be a factory, a warehouse, a regional distribution center, or a service center. ","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"The material master is the most commonly used organizational data in an enterprise.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"The material master includes a large amount of data because it is used in numerous processes.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Materials are categorized into different material types based on the way they are used in the firm’s operations.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"The four most common material types are raw materials, semi‐finished goods, finished goods, and exported goods. ","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Raw materials (ROH) are purchased from an external source ‐ a vendor‐ and used in the production process.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Trading goods (HAWA) are resold to customers after they have been modified by the company.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Transaction data reflect the consequences of executing process steps.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"The financial accounting documents, management accounting or controlling documents, and material documents are all \'virtual.\'","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Reporting is a general term for the methods a user can utilize to update data in the ERP system to execute process steps.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"The online transaction processing (OLTP) system is designed to capture and store detailed organizational data.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Work lists identify tasks that are scheduled to be completed in a process.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Information structures display lists of master data, such as materials, vendors, and purchasing info records, and documents, such as transaction documents, FI, CO, and material documents that are generated during the execution of a process.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1}]}';
var text2 = '{"quizName":"ERP Quiz 4","questions":[{"question":"Which one of the following is not a type of organizational data that is utilized in the procurement process?","options":["Client","Company Code","Storage Location","Purchasing Organization","Manufacturing Plant"],"answerIndex":4},{"question":"What is a storage location? ","options":["The place where raw materials are received","The place within a plant where materials are kept until they are needed","The place where materials are collected for staging and inspection","The place within a plant where machines are installed for production purposes","The place within a plant where finished goods are kept for sale"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Which organizational element(s) control(s) the entry of accounting data in the vendor master?","options":["Purchasing organization","Client","Company Code","Client and Company Code","Client and Purchasing Organization"],"answerIndex":3},{"question":"A purchasing organization is involved in all of the following operations except","options":["Negotiating contracts and agreements","Negotiating pricing with vendors","Evaluating and identifying vendors","Determining storage locations within the plant"],"answerIndex":3},{"question":"Which one of the following is not a model of the purchasing organization?","options":["Enterprise level","Company level","Client level","Plant level","Cross-plant"],"answerIndex":2},{"question":" Within the plant-level purchasing organization, also known as a plant-specific purchasing organization, ","options":["Each plant has its own purchasing organization","One purchasing organization is responsible for multiple plants","Only one purchasing organization for all plants","One purchasing organization is responsible for all company codes in the enterprise","Two or more purchasing organizations are responsible for each plant"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"A purchasing group is an individual or a group of individuals who are responsible for all of the following except","options":["Creating purchase requisitions","Negotiating contracts and agreements","Requesting quotations from vendors","Creating and monitoring purchase orders","Planning for material requirements"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Which one of the following is not one of the data types that are relevant to the purchasing process? ","options":["Material master","Vendor master","Sales master","Purchasing info records","Conditions"],"answerIndex":2},{"question":"The key data in the purchasing view of the material master are ","options":["The purchasing organization, the goods receipt processing time, and the delivery tolerances","The purchasing group, the goods receipt processing time, and the delivery tolerances","The purchasing group, the invoice, and the delivery tolerances","The purchasing group, the material master, and the delivery tolerances","The price, the storage location, and the delivery date"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Data in the vendor master are grouped into which three segments? ","options":["General data, storage data, and purchasing data","General data, storage data, and inventory data","Storage data, accounting data, and purchasing data","Storage data, accounting data, and pricing data","General data, accounting data, and purchasing data"],"answerIndex":4},{"question":"General data in a vendor master contain all of the following except:","options":["Name","Address","Communication","Payment terms and methods","Search term"],"answerIndex":3},{"question":"Which of the following is an intersection or combination of material data and vendor data?","options":["Condition type","Purchasing info record","Stock transfer","Third-party order","Search term"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Which item category would you use to have your vendor ship goods directly to your customer?","options":["Consignment","Third-party","Stock transfer","Standard","Transfer posting"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Materials that are acquired to be used within the organization are referred to as","options":["Stock materials","Transfer materials","Vendor materials","Consumable materials","None of the above"],"answerIndex":3},{"question":"Which of the following account assignment categories is used when the company acquires a fixed asset?","options":["Cost center","Asset","Order","Sales order","Project"],"answerIndex":2},{"question":"Which of the following document types is not utilized during the Purchasing process?","options":["Material documents","Fl documents","CO documents","Picking document","Invoice"],"answerIndex":3},{"question":"A FI document includes a header and an items section.  Which of the following data are included in the items section?","options":["Document number","Account","Storage location","Document date","Document currency"],"answerIndex":2},{"question":"Which of the following statements about a plant is not true?","options":["A plant can be assigned to more than one company code","A company code can have more than one plant","A plant is a key organizational element in purchasing","A plant can be assigned to only one company code","A plant must have at least one storage area"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Which of the following goods movements need not involve a physical movement of materials?","options":["Goods receipt","Goods issue","Stock transfer","Transfer posting","None of the above (all involve physical movement of materials)"],"answerIndex":3},{"question":"Which element of the requirements determination process involves creating the requisition?","options":["Data","Task","Trigger","Outcomes","None of the above"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"A company can use which of the following to select a vendor from a list of potential suppliers ?","options":["Source list","Company code","Vendor master","Material master","None of the above"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Which element of a purchase order includes communicating with the vendor?","options":["Trigger","Data","Task","Outcome","None of the above"],"answerIndex":3},{"question":"Which item is included in the header of a purchase order?","options":["Order quantity","Vendor","Delivery date","Price","None of the above"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"SAP can utilize which of the following media to communicate with a vendor?","options":["Material ordered","Quantity delivered","Verification","Storage location","All of the above"],"answerIndex":4},{"question":"SAP can utilize which of the following media to communicate with a vendor?","options":["Material ordered","Quantity delivered","Verification","Storage location","All of the above"],"answerIndex":4},{"question":"Which of the following is a form of invoice verification?","options":["Three-way match","Quality management","Inspection lot","Warehouse management","None of the above"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Which element of the payment step includes selecting a bank?","options":["Trigger","Data","Outcome","Task","None of the above"],"answerIndex":3},{"question":"Which of the following facilitates the integration between vendor master data and financial accounting?","options":["Vendor account number","Reconciliation account","Accounts payable number","Material number","Accounts receivable number"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Purchasing information systems are a component of which system?","options":["Logistics information systems","Business intelligence systems","Financial information systems","Human resource information systems"],"answerIndex":0}]}';
var text3 = '{"quizName":"ERP Quiz 4","questions":[{"question":"Which one of the following is not a type of organizational data that is utilized in the procurement process?","options":["Client","Company Code","Storage Location","Purchasing Organization","Manufacturing Plant"],"answerIndex":4},{"question":"What is a storage location? ","options":["The place where raw materials are received","The place within a plant where materials are kept until they are needed","The place where materials are collected for staging and inspection","The place within a plant where machines are installed for production purposes","The place within a plant where finished goods are kept for sale"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Which organizational element(s) control(s) the entry of accounting data in the vendor master?","options":["Purchasing organization","Client","Company Code","Client and Company Code","Client and Purchasing Organization"],"answerIndex":3},{"question":"A purchasing organization is involved in all of the following operations except","options":["Negotiating contracts and agreements","Negotiating pricing with vendors","Evaluating and identifying vendors","Determining storage locations within the plant"],"answerIndex":3}]}';
var chapter4 = '{"quizName":"ERP Chapter 4","questions":[{"question":"Which one of the following is not a type of organizational data that is utilized in the procurement process?","options":["Client","Company Code","Storage Location","Purchasing Organization","Manufacturing Plant"],"answerIndex":4},{"question":"What is a storage location? ","options":["The place where raw materials are received","The place within a plant where materials are kept until they are needed","The place where materials are collected for staging and inspection","The place within a plant where machines are installed for production purposes","The place within a plant where finished goods are kept for sale"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Which organizational element(s) control(s) the entry of accounting data in the vendor master?","options":["Purchasing organization","Client","Company Code","Client and Company Code","Client and Purchasing Organization"],"answerIndex":3},{"question":"A purchasing organization is involved in all of the following operations except","options":["Negotiating contracts and agreements","Negotiating pricing with vendors","Evaluating and identifying vendors","Determining storage locations within the plant"],"answerIndex":3},{"question":"Which one of the following is not a model of the purchasing organization?","options":["Enterprise level","Company level","Client level","Plant level","Cross-plant"],"answerIndex":2},{"question":"Within the plant-level purchasing organization, also known as a plant-specific purchasing Organization,","options":["Each plant has its own purchasing organization","One purchasing organization is responsible for multiple plants","Only one purchasing organization for all plants","One purchasing organization is responsible for all company codes in the enterprise","Two or more purchasing organizations are responsible for each plant"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"A purchasing group is an individual or a group of individuals who are responsible for all of the following except","options":["Creating purchase requisitions","Negotiating contracts and agreements","Requesting quotations from vendors","Creating and monitoring purchase orders","Planning for material requirements"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Which one of the following is not one of the data types that are relevant to the purchasing process? ","options":["Material master","Vendor master","Sales master","Purchasing info records","Conditions"],"answerIndex":2},{"question":"The key data in the purchasing view of the material master are ","options":["The purchasing organization, the goods receipt processing time, and the delivery tolerances","The purchasing group, the goods receipt processing time, and the delivery tolerances","The purchasing group, the invoice, and the delivery tolerances","The purchasing group, the material master, and the delivery tolerances","The price, the storage location, and the delivery date"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Data in the vendor master are grouped into which three segments? ","options":["General data, storage data, and purchasing data","General data, storage data, and inventory data","Storage data, accounting data, and purchasing data","Storage data, accounting data, and pricing data","General data, accounting data, and purchasing data"],"answerIndex":4},{"question":"General data in a vendor master contain all of the following except:","options":["Name","Address","Communication","Payment terms and methods","Search term"],"answerIndex":3},{"question":"Which of the following is an intersection or combination of material data and vendor data?","options":["Condition type","Purchasing info record","Stock transfer","Third-party order","Search term"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Which item category would you use to have your vendor ship goods directly to your customer?","options":["Consignment","Third-party","Stock transfer","Standard","Transfer posting"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Materials that are acquired to be used within the organization are referred to as","options":["Stock materials","Transfer materials","Vendor materials","Consumable materials","None of the above"],"answerIndex":3},{"question":"Which of the following account assignment categories is used when the company acquires a fixed asset?","options":["Cost center","Asset","Order","Sales order","Project"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Which of the following document types is not utilized during the Purchasing process?","options":["Material documents","Fl documents","CO documents","Picking document","Invoice"],"answerIndex":3},{"question":"A FI document includes a header and an items section.  Which of the following data are included in the items section?","options":["Document number","Account","Storage location","Document date","Document currency"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Which of the following statements about a plant is not true?","options":["A plant can be assigned to more than one company code","A company code can have more than one plant","A plant is a key organizational element in purchasing","A plant can be assigned to only one company code","A plant must have at least one storage area"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Which of the following goods movements need not involve a physical movement of materials?","options":["Goods receipt","Goods issue","Stock transfer","Transfer posting","None of the above (all involve physical movement of materials)"],"answerIndex":3},{"question":"Which element of the requirements determination process involves creating the requisition?","options":["Data","Task","Trigger","Outcomes","None of the above"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"A company can use which of the following to select a vendor from a list of potential suppliers ?","options":["Source list","Company code","Vendor master","Material master","None of the above"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Which element of a purchase order includes communicating with the vendor?","options":["Trigger","Data","Task","Outcome","None of the above"],"answerIndex":3},{"question":"Which item is included in the header of a purchase order?","options":["Order quantity","Vendor","Delivery date","Price","None of the above"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"SAP can utilize which of the following media to communicate with a vendor?","options":["Web services","EDI","Fax","Print","All of the above"],"answerIndex":4},{"question":"Which of the following is(are) a form of data within the goods receipt step?","options":["Material ordered","Quantity delivered","Verification","Storage location","All of the above"],"answerIndex":4},{"question":"Which of the following is a form of invoice verification?","options":["Three-way match","Quality management","Inspection lot","Warehouse management","None of the above"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Which element of the payment step includes selecting a bank?","options":["Trigger","Data","Outcome","Task","None of the above"],"answerIndex":3},{"question":"Which of the following facilitates the integration between vendor master data and financial accounting?","options":["Vendor account number","Reconciliation account","Accounts payable number","Material number","Accounts receivable number"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Purchasing information systems are a component of which system?","options":["Logistics information systems","Business intelligence systems","Financial information systems","Human resource information systems"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Storage locations are places within a plant were materials are kept until they are needed. ","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"There can only be one storage location within a plant. ","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"A storage location is a key organizational element in purchasing.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"A purchasing organization is involved only in negotiating prices with vendors ","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Typically, there are three models of purchasing organizations: enterprise-level, company-level, and plant-level. ","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"The enterprise‐level purchasing organization is also known as the cross‐company code purchasing organization. ","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"The company-level purchasing organization is the most centralized model.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"The enterprise-level purchasing organization is the most centralized model. ","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"A plant can belong to more than one company code.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"The most decentralized model of purchasing organizations is the plant‐specific purchasing organization.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"A purchasing group is an internal group that is responsible for executing the procurement process.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"A purchasing organization is an individual or a group of individuals who are responsible for purchasing activities for a material or group of materials. ","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Vendor master data include the data needed to conduct business with a vendor and to execute transactions related to the procurement process.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"The method used to value material is defined in the material master.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Different material types have different required material views.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"General data related to a vendor are accessible to all company codes in a client.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Purchasing data related to a vendor are accessible to all purchasing organizations.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Material master data can be defined differently for different organizational levels.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"A purchasing info record is an intersection or combination of material and accounting data.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Accounting data related to a vendor are accessible to all clients in a company code.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Item categories in a purchase order determine the process steps used to procure materials.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Consumable materials are acquired to be used within an organization.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"When purchasing consumable materials, an account assignment category and specific account assignment objects must be provided when the purchase order is created.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"A goods movement is not required when changing the status of material from “in quality inspection” to “unrestricted use”.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"A plant-to-plant movement of goods does not generate an accounting document.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"A goods receipt cannot be accomplished without a movement type.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"A stock transfer does not involve a change in storage location.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"A transfer posting changes the stock status of a material and need not involve a physical movement of goods.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"A goods movement is a transaction that causes a change in stock value or status.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Materials cannot be moved from one company code to another because each company code uses a different set of books.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"A transfer posting is used to move materials from one storage location to another.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"A transfer posting does not generate a material document.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Requirements for materials must be created manually.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"The data needed to create a purchase requisition are the item category, quantity, desired delivery date, and desired delivery location or receiving plant. ","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"A requisition represents a legal obligation to make the purchase.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"The header section of a purchase order contains information such as purchase order number, vendor, currency, dates, and payment terms.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"The primary task of the order processing step is to create and send the purchase order to the vendor.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"SAP cannot utilize any media except Web services to communicate a purchase order to a vendor.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Materials ordered in multiple purchase orders must be delivered in multiple shipments.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"The material master is updated after the invoice verification step of the procurement process has been completed.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"The material master is updated after the goods receipt step of the procurement process has been completed.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Tolerances for price variations among purchase orders, invoices, and goods receipts are allowed, but tolerances for quantity variances are not.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Invoice verification authorizes payment of the invoice to the vendor.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Payments must be made automatically through a payment program.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Electronic payments are sent automatically.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Work lists display lists of master data and documents that are generated during the execution of a process.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1}]}'
var chapter6 = '{"quizName":"ERP Chapter 6","questions":[{"question":"Which one of the following is NOT a type of organizational data relevant to the production process?","options":["Company code","Credit control area","Client","Storage location","Plant"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"In process industries like chemicals and beverages, the bill of materials is also known as a(n)","options":["Formula","List of chemicals","Bill of chemicals","Equation","Material list"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Which one of the following best describes a work center?","options":["A location where materials are placed right before they are shipped","Another term used to describe an office building","A location where value-added work needed to produce a material is carried out","A shipping dock","A storage shelf in a warehouse"],"answerIndex":2},{"question":"All of the following can serve as a work center except","options":["A group of machines","A group of people responsible for completing operations","A production line","A work area","A shipping dock"],"answerIndex":4},{"question":"What term describes two simultaneous series of operations needed to build components for a finished product?","options":["Parallel sequences","Alternate sequences","Same sequence","Line sequence","Production sequence"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Which one of the following best defines material staging?","options":["Component materials are moved into storage","Component materials are received from the vendor","Component materials are moved from storage and prepared for use","Defective returned goods are broken down into several components for refurbishment","Finished materials are moved back into a storage area"],"answerIndex":2},{"question":"What term identifies the list of materials needed to produce one or more units of a finished good?","options":["Routing","Source materials","Component listing","Bill of components","Bill of materials"],"answerIndex":4},{"question":"At what level are material requirements planning (MRP) and work scheduling data defined?","options":["Client level","Plant level","Company code level","Sales area level","Production level"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Which of the following is not a step in the production process?","options":["Production authorization","Goods issue","Request production","Billing","Order release"],"answerIndex":3},{"question":"If a company has adopted the make-to-stock strategy, what is the trigger for the production of goods?","options":["Need to increase inventory","Customer order","Request for quotation","Customer inquiry","Billing document"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Which of the following does a routing identify on a production order?","options":["The materials or components to be used in production","The location where operations are to be performed","The capacity requirements of the production order","The location of raw materials in the warehouse","The operations needed to produce a material"],"answerIndex":4},{"question":"What step in the production process is used to enter data in to the SAP ERP system when the operations needed to produce a materials are completed?","options":["Production note","Confirmation","Order complete","Production record","Production outcome"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"The creation of a production order results in several outcomes including all of the following except","options":["Scheduling","Availability checks","Purchase requisitions","Preliminary costing","Confirmation"],"answerIndex":4},{"question":"What operation in the routing is sometimes necessary to prepare materials for use in production?","options":["Backflushing","Confirmation","Material staging","Recall","Reservation"],"answerIndex":2},{"question":"Which of the following is not an outcome of a goods issue to a production order?","options":["The material master is updated to reflect the reduction in the quantity and value of the materials issued","Actual costs associated with material consumption are calculated","Material reservations are updated","A goods receipt is automatically recorded","An FI document is created to record financial accounting data"],"answerIndex":3},{"question":"When the finished goods have been produced the SAP ERP system allows a user to record which of the following?","options":["Confirmation","Goods issue","Order release","Goods receipt","Authorize production r"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Which of the following is an important report in the production process?","options":["Work list","Stock requirement list","Online list","BOM","None of the above"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"A bill of materials identifies the finished goods that are to be shipped to a specific customer.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"An active bill of materials can be used in the production of a material, but an inactive BOM cannot.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"A work center is a location where materials are placed immediately before they are shipped.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"All operations must be performed in some type of sequence, and many operations can be completed in a variety of sequences.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Fixed time elements represent the time needed to produce one unit of material.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Variable time elements are independent of how many units of material are produced.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Material staging is the process in which component materials are moved from storage and prepared for use.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Component assignment is a technique that assigns components in a BOM either to a routing or to a specific operation within the routing.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Production resource tools are movable resources that are shared among different work centers.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Typically a production order does not include any references to the BOM, routing, or work centers.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Capacity split is a strategy that is used to determine how the production work  is to be distributed among machines and/or people","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"After production has been completed, a goods receipt against the production order is used to pick the goods and ship them to the customer","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"If the bill of materials and the routing data are changed after the production order has been created, the system must be manually instructed to reenter the data","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"A time ticket is used to record the amount of time required to complete various operations","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Material staging is a technique that is used to automatically record the goods issue when an order is confirmed","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Periodic processing is also known as period-end closing","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Overhead allocation, work in process determination, and order settlement are all included in periodic processing","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"A technically complete status for a production order means that even though the main  material is complete, other production processes may be needed to complete smaller components of the material","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1}]}'
var chapter7 = '{"quizName":"ERP Chapter 7","questions":[{"question":"Which of the following statements about the goods receipt step are NOT true?","options":["It results in a decrease in inventory. ","It can occur during the procurement process.","It can result in the creation of material and financial accounting documents. ","Materials are placed in an appropriate storage location with an appropriate status. ","It can occur during the production process."],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"The key organizational level associated with inventory management is ","options":["Plant. ","Company code. ","Storage section. ","Storage area.","Storage location."],"answerIndex":4},{"question":"When do unplanned receipts occur? ","options":["When an invoice has been canceled","When material is transferred to another location","When a reference document does not exist","When a stock transfer is created","When the capacity of a storage location is exceeded"],"answerIndex":2},{"question":"In the production process, a goods issue reflects","options":["Moving raw materials or semi-finished goods from a work center to storage bins.","Shipping finished goods or trading goods to a customer to fill a sales order.","Issuing finished goods to a production order. ","Shipping finished goods to a customer against a goods issue request.","Issuing raw materials or semi-finished goods to a production order."],"answerIndex":4},{"question":"Which of the following scenarios requires material-to-material posting?","options":["Changing the material status from consignment to warehouse stock","Changing the material number of a material","Changing the material�s storage location","Changing the status of materials in stock","Changing the type of materials in stock"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Which one of the following is NOT an example of using transfer postings?","options":["Changing the material status from consignment to warehouse stock","Changing the material number of a material","Changing the material�s storage location","Changing the status of materials in stock","Changing the type of materials in stock"],"answerIndex":2},{"question":"What is a stock transfer used for?","options":["To change the status or type of materials in stock ","To show material movements when a material is received in the warehouse from the vendor�s location ","To indicate that a material-to-material change has been posted","To physically move materials from a storage location to the client�s warehouse","To physically move materials within the enterprise from one organizational level or location to another"],"answerIndex":4},{"question":"Which of the following options is appropriate when two locations are physically close to each other and there is no significant time lag between issue and receipt?","options":["One-step procedure","Two-step procedure","Three-step procedure","Stock transport order","None of the above"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"A storage location-to-storage location transfer involves which of the following? ","options":["A stock transfer among several storage locations of two plants","A stock transfer between two storage locations of two plants","A stock transfer among several storage locations within the same plant","A stock transfer between two storage locations within the same plant ","A stock transfer between or among at least two storage locations within one or more plants"],"answerIndex":3},{"question":"In plant-to-plant transfer, an FI document","options":["Is created in both one-step and two-step movements.","Is created in two-step movements only.","Is created in one-step movements only.","Is not created. "],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Which of the following represents the hierarchy of a warehouse?","options":["Warehouse, storage section, storage type, storage bin  ","Warehouse, storage bin, storage section, storage type","Warehouse, storage type, storage section, storage bin","Warehouse, storage section, storage bin, storage type","Warehouse, storage type, storage bin, storage section"],"answerIndex":2},{"question":"Shelf storage, pallet storage, and rack storage are examples of ","options":["Storage bins. ","Warehouses.","Storage sections.","Storage types.","None of the above"],"answerIndex":3},{"question":"A storage type is a division of a warehouse based on the characteristics of the ","options":["Weight, width, and type","Dimensions and profitability.","Space, materials, and activity.","Price, space, and type.","Usage, price, and dimensions."],"answerIndex":2},{"question":"Fast-moving, slow-moving, heavy, light, large, and small are examples of ","options":["Storage bins. ","Warehouses.","Storage sections.","Storage types.","None of the above."],"answerIndex":2},{"question":"A picking area groups which of the following elements? ","options":["Shelves and pallets","Storage bins, based on similar picking strategies","Materials with similar transportation type","Materials with similar usage","Materials of the same material type"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"If a company stores a material in a storage location that is associated with a warehouse, then it must include additional data ","options":["In the storage location stock view of the material master for that material.","In the basic data view of the material master for that material.","In the general plant data/storage view of the material master for that material.","In the warehouse management view of the material master for that material.","No data need to be added. "],"answerIndex":3},{"question":"Shelves, stacks, and aisles are examples of ","options":["Storage locations.","Coordinate systems for addresses.","Storage sections.","Storage identifiers.","Storage areas."],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Which of the following represents the document used to plan the movement of materials into and out of bins in a warehouse? ","options":["Transfer list","Transfer request","Transfer plan","Transfer order","Transfer requirement"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Which of the following is a request to change the status of the material? ","options":["Posting change notice","Notice for change","Material change list","Status request list","Change request"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"When creating a transfer order, you find that a particular material has to be moved from multiple source bins. Which of the following statements follows from this scenario?","options":["The transfer order will have multiple line items for the material.","More than one transfer order needs to be created.","The material will be written in one line item.","An internal order request will be created to move the material into one source bin.","This scenario is impossible."],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"The ERP system can create transfer orders automatically, but only when ","options":["A destination is known.","The reference document is a transfer requirement   ","A warehouse movement type is specified.","A reference document exists.","Both the plant and the storage location are known."],"answerIndex":3},{"question":"Which of the following represents a possible sequence of steps in the warehouse movement process? ","options":["Create a transfer request, physically move the materials, confirm the movement, retrieve the transfer request","Physically move the materials, confirm the movement, create a transfer request, retrieve the transfer request","Physically move the materials, generate a transfer order, confirm the movement, retrieve the transfer order","Generate a transfer order, retrieve the transfer order. confirm the movement, physically  move the materials","Generate a transfer order, physically move the materials, retrieve the transfer order, confirm the movement"],"answerIndex":4},{"question":"In warehouse management steps associated with the procurement process, the warehouse inventory is calculated as sum of the inventory in the following places: ","options":["Storage sections and storage areas","Warehouse bins and storage sections","Interim storage areas and warehouse bins","Storage locations and storage sections","Storage locations and storage areas"],"answerIndex":2},{"question":"In a stock transfer from a plant where the storage location is warehouse managed to a plant where it is not, which of the following activities occurs at the receiving plant? ","options":["A goods receipt triggers WM process steps.","A simple goods receipt is recorded in IM.","A goods issue triggers WM process steps.","A simple goods issue is recorded in IM. ","None of the above"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"In a bin status report, double-clicking on a bin that contains materials","options":["Produces a drilldown report showing details of the materials. ","Opens a screen that enables you to change which bin is shown on the report.","Produces information about the bin location.","Opens a screen where storage bin information can be configured.","Will not display any data."],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Warehouse management is typically used","options":["By organizations that have small quantities of materials. ","By transportation companies.","By organizations that have either large quantities of materials or an expensive inventory.","By storage companies.","By organizations that demand better reporting for their inventory. "],"answerIndex":2},{"question":"A storage location is a key organizational level associated with inventory management. ","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"The most relevant category of master data in inventory management is the plant.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"A goods receipt cannot be posted without reference to an order.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Planned receipts occur when a reference document, such as a purchase order or a production order does not exist.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"A goods issue results in the creation of appropriate material, FI, and CO documents. ","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"A goods issue, unlike a goods receipt, can be posted without reference to an order. ","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"A goods issue, unlike a goods receipt, results in a decrease in inventory. ","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"A transfer posting always involves an actual movement of materials. ","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"To change a material number you need to create a change request. ","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"In a consignment scenario, when raw materials are consumed in the production process, the status of the materials is changed from warehouse stock to consignment. ","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"A stock transfer involves physically moving materials. ","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"One-step procedure, two-step procedure, and stock transport order are strategies for moving materials. ","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"A material document is created during both the one-step and two-step procedures.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"During the one-step procedure, two material documents are created.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Moving materials between two storage locations within the same plant or different plants is known as storage location-to-storage location transfer. ","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"One-step procedure is possible only when the materials are in unrestricted use at the supplying location.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"When transferring materials between storage locations in the same plant, if quantities are valued in the same way, then no FI document is created.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"In plant-to-plant transfer in the two-step method, the FI document is created at the time of receipt.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"A movement of materials between two plants in different company codes is called a company code-to-company code transfer.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Stock transport orders with delivery include the invoice verification step.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"In stock transport orders with delivery and billing, valuation is based on the purchase price in the STO.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Inventory management keeps track of the quantity of materials in storage location, but it cannot determine their exact location.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"A storage location can be linked to only one warehouse.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"A storage type is a division of a storage section that is based on the characteristics of the space, materials, or activity.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Storage sections represent the physical links between IM and WM.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Shelf storage is an example of a storage type ","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Lightweight materials are designated as fast-moving materials.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"A picking area groups materials with the same material type.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Storage bins are the smallest unit of space in a warehouse.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Transfer requirements can be created manually as well as automatically.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Transfer orders are used to execute warehouse movements.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Transfer orders can only be created automatically.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Target quantities, destination storage type, bin, and quant are examples of line item data in a transfer order.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Transfer orders in the execute warehouse management step can be created with or without a reference document.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"One of the steps of the inventory management process related to procurement is post goods issue.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Inventory management in the production process involves a goods issue and a goods receipt.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"A stock transfer from a storage bin in one warehouse to a storage bin in another warehouse is a possible scenario under which warehouse movements can occur.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1}]}'
var chapter8 = '{"quizName":"ERP Chapter 8","questions":[{"question":"The main objective of material planning is","options":["To minimize the expenses for storing excess inventory. ","To balance the demand for materials with the supply.","To shorten the duration of the procurement cycle. ","To eliminate excess inventory.","To prevent lost sales."],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"The money tied up in inventory best represents","options":["An opportunity cost.","A liquid asset.","A strategic policy.","A high risk for loss.","A material planning strategy. "],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"A purchase requisition is","options":["A confirmation for purchasing materials.","Proof of delivery.","A document issued by a vendor.","A request to purchase materials.","A confirmation of an inbound delivery."],"answerIndex":3},{"question":"Requirements in the material planning process specify","options":["The master data requirements.","How the material planning should be executed.","The work center capacity.","Requirements for the different modes of transportation.","How many of the materials are needed and when they are needed."],"answerIndex":4},{"question":"The organizational data elements in material planning are:","options":["Plant, production version, company code.","Planning version, company code, client.","Client, company code, production version.","Storage section, client, storage location.","Client, company code, plant, storage location."],"answerIndex":4},{"question":"The master data elements in material planning are:","options":["Material masters, product types, storage location, vendors.","Product routings, bills of material, material masters, product groups.","Product types, product routings, material masters, product groups.","Product routings, product types, material masters, customers.","Material masters, storage location, product groups, product routings."],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"A company has two options for procuring materials: make or buy. Which MRP data view of the material master will the ERP system consider for this decision?","options":["MRP 1","MRP 2 ","MRP 3","MRP 4 ","None of the above"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Which of the following statements best represents what procurement type indicates?","options":["How a material is produced","Vendor�s groups","All of the ways to procure a material the user will choose from when making a decision ","Whether a material is produced in house, obtained externally, both, or none","How a vendor will be chosen in the procurement process"],"answerIndex":3},{"question":"MRP type specifies","options":["Whether the material is produced in house or is obtained externally.","How material quantities for planning will be calculated.","The production control technique used in planning.","The available time periods the ERP system can use for scheduling.","The strategy for BOM selection."],"answerIndex":2},{"question":"Replenishment lead time is","options":["The time between placing an order and receiving the materials. ","The amount of time the routing operations will last.","The length of time a working center usually operates (in hrs, in one day).","Another term for capacity.","A synonym for interoperation time."],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Which of the following statements about consumption-based planning is TRUE?","options":["Planning is based on historical data.","Planning is based on exploding the BOM.","Dependent demand is derived from independent demand.","It is used for high-value materials","Planning is based on MPS."],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Which of the following options represents categories of consumption-based planning?","options":["Materials-requirement planning, time-phased planning, reorder-point planning","Master production scheduling, MRP, forecast-based planning","MRP, forecast-based planning, master production scheduling","Forecast-based planning, time-phased planning, reorder-point planning","None of the above"],"answerIndex":3},{"question":"A company would be most likely to apply consumption-based planning for which of the following products?","options":["Car","Brake","Engine","Printer","Pen"],"answerIndex":4},{"question":"The MRP technique calculates the requirements for a material based on","options":["Historical data.","Current data.","The material�s dependence on other materials.","Material type.","Replenishment lead time."],"answerIndex":2},{"question":"Exploding the BOM refers to","options":["Creating the BOM hierarchy showing all the levels of the BOM. ","Calculating and planning requirements for materials at all levels of the BOM.","Executing the BOM for materials at the top level of the BOM.","Choosing the planning strategy for the BOM.","Generating multiple BOMs for materials in the same material group."],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Requirements that are calculated based on actual and forecasted sales are known as","options":["Planned independent requirements.","Customer-planned independent requirements.","Integrated independent requirements.","Forecast-independent requirements.","Customer-independent requirements."],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"The lot size key specifies the","options":["Optimum lot size for a group of materials.","Recommended lot size for a material.","Procedure used to determine the capacity of a storage area.","Lot size groups per each material type.","Procedure that is used to determine the lot size."],"answerIndex":4},{"question":"The static lot-sizing procedure","options":["Combines the requirements from multiple time periods into one lot.","Specifies a fixed quantity based on fixed lot size.","Specifies a quantity that is fixed for a specific, limited time period.","Specifies a fixed quantity based on either fixed lot size or lot-for-lot.","Combines quantities for multiple time periods into several lots."],"answerIndex":3},{"question":"Setup time, processing time, and interoperation time are elements of","options":["In-house production time.","Goods issue processing time.","Planned delivery time.","Goods receipt processing time.","Planned shipping time."],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Setup time is the time required to","options":["Set up the operations used in a work center.","Move materials from one work center to another.","Process materials in production.","Set up the work centers used in production.","Move materials from one storage location to another."],"answerIndex":3},{"question":"In SAP ERP production planning  strategy, net requirements planning (Strategy 10), procurement proposals are based on","options":["CIRs and components that are already in stock.","PIRs, with regard to CIRs.","PIRs, without regard to CIRs.","CIRs, but components are not in stock.","PIRs, but the components are not in stock."],"answerIndex":2},{"question":"Consider the following scenario, then choose which one of the options below corresponds to the level of CIRs and PIRs after consumption. Before consumption: Procurement proposal for CIRs: 50Procurement proposal for PIRs: 50","options":["CIRs: 50, PIRs: 0","CIRs: 50, PIRs: 50","CIRs: 0, PIRs: 0","CIRs: 0, PIRs: 50","CIRs: 100, PIRs: 100"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"The manner in which CIRs consume PIRs is determined by the","options":["Consumption type.","Consumption mode.","Consumption strategy.","Planning strategy.","Planning type."],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"What does SOP stand for?","options":["Sales and operations planning","Strategic operations planning","Sales operations planner","Systems operations products","Sales operations projects"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"What is SOP used for?","options":["Creating an operational plan and material documents","Calculating the financial impact of the material movements","Generating and executing the operations plan","Tracking material movements","Forecasting and planning     "],"answerIndex":4},{"question":"After the SOP process has generated the production plan, ","options":["SOP executes the plan.","The plan is conveyed to MRP for execution.","The plan is transferred to demand management.","SOP uses the plan to generate execution plan. ","The plan is saved as a production version."],"answerIndex":2},{"question":"The planning table is best defined as","options":["An independent tool used for parallel execution of the SOP process.","An interface for transferring data into SOP.","An interface used to enter all the operational plans.","A spreadsheet-like tool used to complete the tasks in SOP. ","A brainstorming session for selecting the most appropriate plan. "],"answerIndex":3},{"question":"Given the information below, calculate disaggregated quantities for touring bikes (TOUR) and off-road bikes (ORBK). Total production = 100 TOUR proportion factor = 35 ORBK proportion factor = 65","options":["TOUR = 35, ORBK = 65","TOUR = 65, ORBK = 35","TOUR = 0, ORBK = 65","TOUR = 35, ORBK = 0","TOUR = 50, ORBK = 50"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Master production scheduling is specialized form of","options":["MRP.","Demand planning.","SOP.","Production planning.","Operations scheduling."],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Given the following information, use the net requirement calculation to calculate the available stock. MRP type is consumption-based planning. Plant stock = 100 Receipts = 20 Issues = 10 Safety stock = 30","options":["120","130","80","70","110"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Given the following information, use the net requirement calculation to calculate the available stock. MRP type is MPS. Plant stock = 100 Receipts = 20 Issues = 10 Safety stock = 30","options":["120","130","80","70","110"],"answerIndex":2},{"question":"In the determine procurement proposal step, for materials with the procurement type of internal, MRP will:","options":["Generate purchase requisitions.","Provide three options.","Prompt the MRP controller to select the appropriate production version. ","Transfer this step to MPS.","Always generate planned orders."],"answerIndex":4},{"question":"Which of the following is most likely to trigger the MRP process?","options":["A periodic planning need","Changes to MRP elements","The need for an operations plan","Events affecting demand","Events affecting supply"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"The most important reporting tool in material planning is the","options":["Planning result report.","MRP list.","Stock overview.","Stock/requirements list.","Strategies list."],"answerIndex":3},{"question":"The stock/requirements list displays","options":["Changes in the planning situation since MRP was run.","MRP elements at an aggregation level.","All MRP elements for a material.","Required materials per production version.","All materials needed per MRP element."],"answerIndex":2},{"question":"Lack of overall planning may result in excess inventory and lost sales.","options":[],"answerIndex":0},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":1},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":0},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":0},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":0},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":1},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":0},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":1},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":0},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"   ","options":["Semifinished goods are typically purchased from vendors"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"MRP type specifies the production control technique used in planning. ","options":[],"answerIndex":1},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":0},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":1},{"question":null,"options":["In a scenario when the need for brakes depends on the need to produce cars, consumption-based planning will be an appropriate strategy to use."],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Typically, semi-finished goods and raw materials have dependent requirements. ","options":[],"answerIndex":1},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":1},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":0},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":0},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":1},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":0},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":0},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":1},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":0},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":1},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":0},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":1},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":1},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":1},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":1},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":1},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":0},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":0},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":1},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":0},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":0},{"question":" ","options":["Net requirements calculation is one of the steps in MRP. "],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"The lot size calculation step in MRP is used to determine whether there is a need to procure the material. ","options":[],"answerIndex":0},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":1},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":0},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":1},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":1}]}'